the television factory has released this
la fábrica de la tele ha lanzado este
statement regarding the news of the
comunicado respecto a la noticias de los
last few days confirming that it will not be
últimos días que confirmaba que no va a
working with mediaset again
volver a trabajar con mediaset
officially socialite will no longer be
oficialmente socialite ya no será
produced by the television factory The
producida por la fábrica de la tele El
Chester either and it's all a lie they do
Chester tampoco y todo es mentira
n't change producers but they are
tampoco cambian de productora pero se
staying with media set but María Patiño No she has
quedan en media set pero María Patiño No
already posted several tweets dropping
ya ha puesto varios tweets dejando caer
the possibility and sowing the
como la posibilidad y sembrando ahí el
game and the doubt that they have something
juego y la duda de que tienen algo
prepared for her or rather the truth is
preparado para ella o sea la verdad es
that she is playing with the ambiguity
que está como jugando con la ambigüedad
of Haha You don't know everything You don't know what's
de Jaja No lo sabéis todo No sabéis la
coming you're going to get hit eh I'm
que se viene os vais a llevar un palo eh
staying here eh I don't know what
que yo me quedo por aquí eh No sé lo que
they have planned the truth but this
tendrán planeado la verdad Pero esto me
smells like a ghost to me sincerely I think it
huele a fantasmada sinceramente creo que
's a way of self-protection from how
es una manera de autoprotege de lo
sad she is in fact today she hasn't
triste que está de hecho ya hoy no ha
gone to socialite today on socialite Javier
ido a socialité hoy en socialité Javier
de hoyo has announced that María Patiño had
de hoyo ha anunciado que María Patiño
not been able to go to work
pues no había podido acudir a su trabajo
and people well think that María well is not
y la gente pues piensa que María pues no
going through a
está pasando en estos momentos por un
very busy time at the moment let's say
momento muy animado que digamos